dxi.eu 2015-11-07

# Connect to DXI and Communicate with the World | DXI

##  Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy outlines how DXI Limited (referred to as “we”, “us” or “DXI”) uses the personal information that we collect via our website at http://www.dxi.eu (the “Site”) and as otherwise described below. It also provides information about how we use cookies.

By visiting the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as they may be amended from time to time.

##  What information do we collect from you?

To use our products and services, you will need to register with us and pay for such products and services. During the registration/payment process, we may collect personal data relating to individuals, including name, address, email address, telephone number and/or payment card details. We may also collect personal data relating to individuals in the context of our reseller programme, if you register as a third party distributor of our services. Personal data may also be provided to us when you correspond with us (for example, when you send us an email using the email address provided on the website).

We also collect certain information automatically about visitors to the Site, as described in our Cookies Policy

If you provide us with information about another person, you confirm that you have obtained their consent to the processing of their personal data by us and that you have informed them of our identity and the purposes for which their personal data will be processed (as set out in this Privacy Policy).

**How we use your information**

We use the information we collect from you for the following purposes:

  * To process your payment and to provide you with the information, products or services that you have requested from us;
  * To respond to your correspondence, so that we can reply to your enquiries and requests in an efficient and effective manner;
  * To enable you to register with the Site, and to administer records about your DXI Limited account;
  * To understand the interests of the Site visitors, so that we can continuously improve our website offering;
  * To notify you about special offers on our products and services that may be of interest to you.

##  With whom do we share your information?

To protect your credit, debit or charge card against use without your consent, we may validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you during the order process against appropriate third party databases. In performing these checks, personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity, that a credit check is not performed and that your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

We may share your personal information with our service providers and agents for the provision of services to DXI Limited or on its behalf. We do not authorise these third parties to use or disclose your personal data except for the purposes of providing the services we request of them.

From time to time, we may disclose your personal information to any third party that purchases all or substantially all of our assets and business, as well as to any law enforcement agency, court, regulator, government authority or other third party where we believe this is necessary to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation, or otherwise to protect our rights or the rights of any third party.

We may also generate, use and disclose aggregated and/or anonymised information and statistics about visitors to the Site for marketing and strategic purposes. However, no visitor will be individually identifiable from these aggregated and/or anonymised information and statistics.

##  Collection and use of your customers’ personal information by you when using our products and services

By registering with us and setting up a campaign, you will be using our products and services to make calls to and/or receive calls from your customers. You acknowledge that you are the data controller of the personal data relating to your customers and are responsible for complying with any obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998 and any other applicable legislation, including without limitation in respect of any live interception of the calls between you and your customers and any recording and storage of those calls.

If your customers have queries or complaints in respect of your campaign, you agree that you will ask them to direct these queries/complaints to you and you discharge and indemnify us from any and all liabilities originating from your dealings with your customers.

##  Your rights

You have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information that we hold about you in our records, to correct any inaccuracies and to update any out-of-date information. Please contact us at the email address listed below should you wish to do so.

Please note that we are entitled to charge a small fee (currently £25) for providing you with copies of personal information we may hold about you.

##  Security

Security is very important to us. SSL encryption technology is used for protection of information in transit for any sensitive transactions such as payments. Additional security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of your personal information.

While we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the security of personal data, as outlined above, you understand and agree that the Internet has inherent vulnerabilities and that no security system can be guaranteed 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee security in respect of the information that you transmit through the Site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this Privacy Policy. When we do so we will publish the changes on the Site. If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to use the Site. If material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Site. Any queries or comments about this Privacy Policy should be sent to us using the contact details listed below.

##  Contact details

If you need to contact us regarding our Privacy Policy or any other related issue please write to:

Legal Department

DXI Limited   
21 New Street  
London  
EC2M 4TP

or email: [info@dxi.eu](mailto:info@dxi.eu?subject=Privacy%20Policy)
